{
    "subject": "resource/One_(Creed_song)",
    "predicate": "ontology/album",
    "object": "resource/My_Own_Prison",
    "human_readable": "The album of the song One is My Own Prison.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9788727760314941,
            "question": "What album contains the song 'One Is My Own Prison'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9629532098770142,
            "question": "Which artist released the album containing 'One Is My Own Prison'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9107563495635986,
            "question": "Where was the album containing 'One Is My Own Prison' recorded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9000495076179504,
            "question": "What year was the album containing 'One Is My Own Prison' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8875752091407776,
            "question": "Are there any other popular songs on the same album as 'One Is My Own Prison'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8776506781578064,
            "question": "What genre of music does the album containing 'One Is My Own Prison' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8469536900520325,
            "question": "Is there a specific theme explored in the song 'One Is My Own Prison'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8442155122756958,
            "question": "Did the release of the album containing 'One Is My Own Prison' receive critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7919180989265442,
            "question": "Has the song 'One Is My Own Prison' been covered by other artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6657624244689941,
            "question": "What is the overall mood or feeling conveyed by the song 'One Is My Own Prison'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The album of the song One is My Own Prison.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3746_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has the song 'One Is My Own Prison' been covered by other artists?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3746_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did the release of the album containing 'One Is My Own Prison' receive critical acclaim?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3746_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a specific theme explored in the song 'One Is My Own Prison'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3746_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3746_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3746_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3746_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3746_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3746_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3746_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3746_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3746_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3746_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3746_47.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"One\" is a track from the album \"My Own Prison,\" which was released in 1997. Therefore, the statement \"The album of the song One is My Own Prison\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}